[Music]
Good morning everyone again I am a
full-time financial wealth Planner here on
fwd Our mission here is We
want to change how people feel about
insurance if you are the one
asking What do
we really feel when someone takes out
life insurance you don't have to answer
because we already know the answer
most of us We will think that our
beneficiaries will the proceeds when
we are gone right
my family will only get that when I die but
then again that's reality
we will really die We just don't know
when okay but most people don't know
that there is this so-called living
benefits Okay what are those living
benefits that are two so there's
medical benefits and there is a growing
fund on the side depending on what
kind of product or what we took
with the medical benefits Including
the critical illness benefit like
when we have major critical
illnesses or even minor we have
money to pay for the
ongoing expenses of
our family's life because we are
unable to work already but not yet
We are dead. Okay, that's our life. We just
get it when we are diagnosed with an illness.
Another is hospital income. So this one
is an allowance per day that is given
in case we are still admitted to the
hospital for a minimum of 2 days. Okay, so with
that we will get this amount once we get
out of the hospital.
daily no that you don't have income on those
days that you are not on duty because of
the
hospitalization Okay so those are just
some of the medical benefits that you
will get now we are still alive if
you have your own plan The other benefit
that I would like to share with
you is the growing funds So how can it be done
quickly Ong earn money after how many
months I can immediately see the returns
of course not no Because when it comes to
investing you should Look at it long
term really when we say long term  It's
estimated
10 years 15  or 20 years or more '
when our fund matures
then we are ready to use it Where are
these growing funds used?
Some are used for their retirement, some are used for
their children's education, some are used to buy
properties, some are used to buy
or get tickets if they want to
travel abroad or Europe, right? So it
really depends on your goal. That's the time you
withdraw if you already have that goal
after certain years. Now, when
you asked me, where should you
invest the money? When you say growing
funds, it always depends on your
aggressiveness when it comes to
investing. You want to be
conservative. We are afraid of losses.
When we want gains or
increases on our invested funds, we should
be aggressive. There is a risk. It is
possible to fall. It is also possible to rise. So we have been
drinking so far. Now with us, we invest
with Ayalaland, Jollibee, Metrobank, Pedo,
Smdc and many others. Okay, so those
companies. You are already a Part owner.
Okay, you have stocks that you have invested in. Even though it is small, that's not a big deal.
or big you are part
and take note with the growing funds you
don't have to monitor it every single
day you don't have to focus on it
every day you just have to trust your
fund manager and they are the ones who
will manage your funds not advisors
okay fund managers are the ones who manage
our funds Okay so that is a lesson
for us all that you don't have to
die to benefit from a life
insurance policy there is actually something
called living benefits